(Sheldon:)My new computer came with
Windows 7.
(Sheldon:)Windows 7 is much more user-friendly
than Windows Vista.
(Sheldon:)I don't like that.
(Leonard:)Don't you think looking for a new city
to live in is a bit of an overreaction?
(Sheldon:)Our apartment was broken into.
(Sheldon:)Our security system tried to kill me.
(Sheldon:)And as a result, I'm leaving Pasadena
forever. Tell me how that's overreacting.
(Penny:)Come on, Sheldon. You can't move.
Don't you need to stay in one place...
(Penny:)...so the mother ship can find you
when it returns?
(Sheldon:)Oh, if that were only true.
(Sheldon:)Unfortunately, as I'm earthbound
for the foreseeable future...
(Sheldon:)...I need to find a location
that's more hospitable...
(Sheldon:)...than the mean streets of Pasadena.
Like Enid, Oklahoma.
(Sheldon:)Low crime rate,
and high-speed Internet connectivity...
...but no model-train shops.
(Sheldon:)Sorry, Enid.